A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1982-1986, RG 37 FA1504
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1982-1986; 37; 327.55 Cubic Feet 857 containers
  - Rockefeller Family Fund, 1982-1986; 28; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
    - Grants (Box 779, Folder 3)
    - Minutes-Meetings (Box 779, Folder 4-5, Box 780, Folder 1)
    - Schrivner, Robert W. (Box 780, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller Family Office, 1979-1983; 29; 7.12 Cubic Feet 17 letter document boxes, 1 half-letter document box and 1 legal box
    - Rockefeller Family and Associates (Box 783, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Open 2042
    - Rockefeller Family and Associates - Benefits, 1980-1986 (Box 784, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Family and Associates - Report to the Board of Directors, 1979 (Box 783, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Family Office - General, 1979-1983 (Box 781, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Family Office - A-Z (Box 781, Folder 3, Box 782, Folder 1)
    - Acadia Risk Management (Box 782, Folder 2)
    - Christmas Party (Box 782, Folder 3)
    - Cousins and Fifth Generation Presentation, 1986 (Box 782, Folder 4)
    - 5600 Inc. (Box 782, Folder 5)
    - 5600 Inc. - Room 5600 (Box 782, Folder 6)
    - 5600 Inc. - Room 5600 - Staff Retreat, 1985 (Box 782, Folder 7)
    - 5600 Inc. - David Rockefeller Office Redecoration (Box 783, Folder 3)
    - 5600 Inc. - David Rockefeller Office Redecoration - Outer Lobby-Elevator (Box 785, Folder 1)
    - 5600 Inc. - Laurance S. Rockefeller Officer Renovations (Box 785, Folder 2)
    - Files-Archives (Box 786, Folder 1)
    - Finances (Box 785, Folder 3)
    - General Files (Box 786, Folder 2)
    - Management (Box 786, Folder 3)
    - Matching Gifts (Box 786, Folder 4)
    - Personnel - A-Z (Box 784, Folder 2-3)
    - Dr. Pounds (Newsletters) (Box 786, Folder 5)
    - Public Affairs - A (Box 780, Folder 3-4)
    - Public Affairs - B-Z (Box 787, Folder 1-5)
    - Public Affairs - Family News Summary, 1983-1986 (Box 788, Folder 1-2)
      Summaries of published articles and media activity
    - Public Affairs - Forbes Magazine (Box 788, Folder 3-5, Box 789, Folder 1)
      Including but not limited to: The Forbes 400.
    - Public Affairs - Greensward Foundation (Box 789, Folder 2-3)
    - Public Affairs - Town and Country (Box 789, Folder 4)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - A-B (Box 789, Folder 5-7)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - C-L (Box 790, Folder 1-4)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - M-S (Box 791, Folder 1-4)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - T-Z (Box 792, Folder 1)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - John D. Rockefeller Jr. Credo (Box 792, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller and Company - A-B (Box 786, Folder 6-7)
    - Rockefeller and Company - C-L (Box 793, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller and Company - M-Z (Box 793, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Board of Directors (Box 793, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Discovery Funds (Box 793, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller and Company - 5500 Fund (Box 793, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Finances (Box 794, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Floating Through America, Inc. (Box 794, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller and Company - John McMahan Associates (Box 794, Folder 3-4, Box 795, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Minutes-Meetings (Box 795, Folder 3, Box 796, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Odyssey Fund (Box 796, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Pocantico Fund (Box 797, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Pocantico Fund - Quarterly Report (Box 797, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Rockefeller Balanced Fund (Box 797, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Rockefeller Capital Fund (Box 797, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Sutter Hotel Associates (Box 798, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller and Company - The Terramics Properties Group (Box 798, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Insurance Company (Box 798, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Trust Company (Box 798, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Trust Company - Meetings (Box 798, Folder 5)
    - Venrock (Box 792, Folder 3-4)
    - Venrock - Apple Computer (Box 792, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1982-1986; 30; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Rockefeller Foundation - A-Z (Box 799, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - Annual Reports, 1980-1986 (Box 799, Folder 4-5)
      Includes Rockefeller Foundation Annual Reports for 1980, 1982, 1984, and 1985
  - Rockefeller University, 1982-1986; 31; 1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes
    - Rockefeller University - A-B (Box 799, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller University - C-Z (Box 800, Folder 1-5)
    - Articles (Box 800, Folder 6)
    - Contributions (Box 800, Folder 7)
    - Contributions - Cousins (Box 798, Folder 6)
    - Finances (Box 801, Folder 1)
    - Fairfield Osborne Memorial Lecture (Box 801, Folder 2)
    - Printed Material (Box 801, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center (RAC) (Box 801, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center (RAC) - Minutes-Meetings (Box 801, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center (RAC) - Printed Material (Box 801, Folder 6)
    - Scholars Residence (Box 801, Folder 7)
  - S, 1982-1986; 32; 7.6 Cubic Feet 20 letter document boxes
    - S - Miscellaneous (Box 801, Folder 8)
    - Science - A-P (Box 802, Folder 1-6)
    - Science - Q-Z (Box 803, Folder 1)
    - Science - Center for Science in the Public Interest (Box 803, Folder 2-4)
    - Science - Center for Science in the Public Interest - Printed Matter (Box 803, Folder 5-6)
    - Science - Committee for Responsible Genetics (Box 804, Folder 1)
    - Science - Federation of American Scientists Fund (Box 804, Folder 2-3)
    - Science - Institute of Noetic Sciences (Box 804, Folder 4)
    - Science - institute of Society, Ethics and the Life Sciences (Box 805, Folder 1)
    - Science - International Student Pugwash, Inc. (Box 805, Folder 2)
    - Science - New Alchemy Institute (Box 805, Folder 3)
    - Science - New Alchemy Institute - Printed Matter (Box 806, Folder 1)
    - Science - Ocean Arks International (Box 806, Folder 2-3)
    - Science - Union of Concerned Scientists (Box 806, Folder 4-5, Box 807, Folder 1-3)
    - Science - Union of Concerned Scientists - Printed Material (Box 807, Folder 4)
    - Seal Harbor Organizations - A-N (Box 807, Folder 5)
    - Seal Harbor Organizations - O-Z (Box 808, Folder 1)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations (Box 808, Folder 2)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - By-Laws (Box 808, Folder 3)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - A-N (Box 808, Folder 4-6)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - O-Z (Box 809, Folder 1-2)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Board of Trustees (Box 809, Folder 3)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Contributions (Box 809, Folder 4-5)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Contributions - Dr. Albert Berger's Research Project Manuscript (Box 810, Folder 1-3)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Croton Associates (Box 810, Folder 4)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Employees (Box 798, Folder 7)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Finances, 1982-1986 (Box 810, Folder 5, Box 811, Folder 1-3)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Fundraising (Box 812, Folder 1-4)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Fundraising - Hudson Valley Cruise (Box 812, Folder 5)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Hudson River Valley (Box 812, Folder 6)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Long Range Planning Committee (Box 813, Folder 1)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Minutes-Meetings, 1982-1983 (Box 813, Folder 2-3)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Minutes-Meetings, 1983-1984 (Box 814, Folder 1-3)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Minutes-Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 815, Folder 1-6, Box 816, Folder 1-2)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Montgomery Place (Box 816, Folder 3)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Pocantico Historic District, 1983-1986 (Box 816, Folder 4)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Pocantico Historic District, 1979-1982 (Box 817, Folder 1-3)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Pocantico Historic District - Sasaki Associates, Inc. (Box 817, Folder 4)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Pocantico Historic District - Union Church of Pocantico Hills (Box 818, Folder 1)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Printed Material and Clippings (Box 818, Folder 2-3, Box 819, Folder 1-2)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Private Foundation Status (Box 819, Folder 3)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Tourism (Box 819, Folder 4-5)
  - T-W, 1982-1986; 33; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - T - Miscellaneous (Box 820, Folder 1)
    - U - Miscellaneous (Box 820, Folder 2)
    - V - Miscellaneous (Box 820, Folder 3)
    - W - Miscellaneous (Box 820, Folder 4)
    - Westchester Organizations (Box 839, Folder 3)
  - Welfare, 1982-1986; 34; 7.6 Cubic Feet 20 letter document boxes
    - Welfare - A-H (Box 820, Folder 5-7)
    - Welfare - H-Q (Box 821, Folder 1-5)
    - Welfare - R-Z (Box 822, Folder 1-3)
    - Actors' Fund of America (Box 822, Folder 4)
    - American Red Cross (Box 822, Folder 5)
    - Center for Community Change, 1982-1986 (Box 823, Folder 1-2)
    - Community Service Society of New York (Box 823, Folder 3)
    - International Human Assistance Programs (Box 823, Folder 4)
    - Jericho Project (Box 823, Folder 5)
    - Massachusetts Fair Share (Box 824, Folder 1)
    - National Sharecroppers Fund (Box 824, Folder 2)
    - New York City Department for the Aging (Box 824, Folder 3)
    - New York City Court Appointed Special Advocates Program (Box 824, Folder 4)
    - Neighborhood Coalition for Shelter, Inc. (Box 824, Folder 5)
    - Tune In (Box 824, Folder 6)
    - United Service Organizations (USO) (Box 825, Folder 1)
    - United Service Organizations - Metropolitan New York (Box 825, Folder 2)
    - Vista (Box 825, Folder 3)
    - Visiting Nurse Service of New York (Box 825, Folder 4)
    - Animals - A-Z (Box 826, Folder 1)
    - Animals - American Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (Box 826, Folder 2)
    - Animals - Animal Medical Center (Box 826, Folder 3)
    - Animals - Animal Welfare Institute (Box 826, Folder 4)
    - Animals - Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (Box 826, Folder 5)
    - Blind - A-Z (Box 826, Folder 6)
    - Blind - Eye Bank for Sight Restoration, Inc. (Box 827, Folder 1)
    - Blind - Recording for the Blind, Inc. (Box 827, Folder 2)
    - Community Centers - A-K (Box 827, Folder 3-4)
    - Community Centers - L-Z (Box 828, Folder 1-2)
    - Community Centers - Fifth Avenue Community Center of Harlem, Inc. (Box 828, Folder 3)
    - Community Centers - Lennox Hill Neighborhood Association (Box 828, Folder 4)
    - Crime Prevention - A-M (Box 828, Folder 5)
    - Crime Prevention - N-Z (Box 829, Folder 1)
    - Crime Prevention - The Eisenhower Foundation for the Prevention of Violence (Box 829, Folder 2-4)
    - Crime Prevention - Morality in Media, Inc. (Box 829, Folder 5)
    - Day Nurseries (Box 830, Folder 1-2)
    - Family Counseling - A-Z (Box 830, Folder 3-4)
    - Family Counseling - Family Service Association of America (Box 830, Folder 5)
    - Family Counseling - Family Service Association of Nassau County (Box 831, Folder 1)
    - Handicapped - A-M (Box 831, Folder 2-5)
    - Handicapped - N-Z (Box 832, Folder 1-3)
    - Handicapped - International Center for the Disabled (Box 832, Folder 4)
    - Handicapped - International Center for the Disabled - Laurance S. Rockefeller (LSR) (Box 833, Folder 1)
    - Handicapped - MDI - Sheltered Workshop (Box 833, Folder 2)
    - Homes - A-Z (Box 833, Folder 3-4)
    - Homes - Coalition for the Homeless (Box 834, Folder 1)
    - Homes - Partnership for the Homeless (Box 834, Folder 2)
    - Native American Indians/Native Americans - A-I (Box 834, Folder 3-4)
    - Native American Indians/Native Americans - J-Z (Box 835, Folder 1-2)
    - Native American Indians/Native Americans - Indian Law Resource Center (Box 835, Folder 3)
    - Native American Indians/Native Americans - Native American Rights Fund (Box 835, Folder 4)
    - Legal - A-Z (Box 836, Folder 1-2)
    - Legal - Citizens Legal Clinic (Box 836, Folder 3-4)
    - Legal - Legal Aid Society (Box 836, Folder 5)
    - Musicians (Box 837, Folder 1)
    - Orphans (Box 837, Folder 2)
    - United Funds - United Way - A-Z (Box 837, Folder 3-4)
    - United Funds - United Way of the Tri-State (Box 837, Folder 5)
    - United Funds - United Way of the Tri-State - Office Campaign 1982, 1982-1983 (Box 837, Folder 6)
    - United Funds - United Way of the Tri-State - Office Campaign 1983-1985, 1983-1986 (Box 838, Folder 1-5)
    - United Funds - United Way of the Tri-State Office Campaign 1986 (Box 839, Folder 1-2)
  - Women, 1982-1986; 35; 1.9 Cubic Feet 5 letter document boxes
    - Women - A-E (Box 839, Folder 4)
    - Women - F-V (Box 840, Folder 1-5)
    - Women - W-Z (Box 841, Folder 1)
    - "Catalyst" (Box 841, Folder 2)
    - Coalition on Women and the Budget (Box 841, Folder 3)
    - Ms. Foundation for Women, 1982-1986 (Box 841, Folder 4)
    - National Organization for Women and Now Legal Defense and Education Fund (Box 841, Folder 5)
    - National Institute for Women of Color (Box 842, Folder 1)
    - National Women's Health Network, Inc. (Box 842, Folder 2)
    - National Women's Law Center (Box 842, Folder 3)
    - Women For Economic Justice (Box 842, Folder 4)
    - Women and Foundations-Corporate Philanthropy (Box 842, Folder 5)
    - Women's Action Alliance, Inc. (Box 842, Folder 6)
    - Women's Equality Action League (Box 842, Folder 7)
    - Women's League Defense Fund (Box 842, Folder 8)
    - Wonder Woman Foundation (Box 843, Folder 1)
  - Youth, 1982-1986; 36; 5.03 Cubic Feet 12 letter document boxes and 1 legal document box
    - Youth - A-Z, 1
      - Youth - A-C (Box 843, Folder 3-5)
      - Youth - D-N (Box 844, Folder 1-4)
      - Youth - O-Z (Box 845, Folder 1-4)
      - Act Together (Box 845, Folder 5)
      - Boy Scouts of America - A-Z (Box 845, Folder 6)
      - Boy Scouts of America - Greater New York Councils (Box 846, Folder 1)
      - Boys' Club of New York (Box 846, Folder 2)
      - Boys Club of America (Box 846, Folder 3)
      - Boys Clubs of St. Croix, Inc. (Box 846, Folder 4)
      - Child Find, Inc. (Box 847, Folder 1)
      - Children's Aid Society (Box 847, Folder 2)
      - Children's Cultural Foundation, Inc. (Box 847, Folder 3)
      - Citizens' Committee for Children of New York, Inc. (Box 847, Folder 4)
      - Covenant House (Box 848, Folder 1)
      - Bing Crosby Youth Fund (Box 848, Folder 2)
      - Girl Scouts of America (Box 848, Folder 3-4)
      - Hugh O'Brian Youth Foundation (Box 848, Folder 5)
      - Infant Formula Action Coalition (Box 849, Folder 1)
      - Police Athletic League, Inc. (PAL) (Box 849, Folder 2)
      - Chi Chi Rodriguez Foundation (Box 849, Folder 3-4, Box 850, Folder 1)
      - Save the Children Federation, Inc. (Box 850, Folder 2)
      - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) (Box 850, Folder 3)
      - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) of Greater New York (Box 850, Folder 4-5)
      - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) of Greater New York - Camping Benefit, 1982-1985 (Box 850, Folder 6)
      - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) (Box 851, Folder 1-2)
      - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - Contributions (Box 851, Folder 3)
      - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board (Box 851, Folder 4)
      - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board - Contributions (Box 851, Folder 5)
      - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board - Printed Matter (Box 852, Folder 1)
    - The Youth Project, 2
      - The Youth Project - General Correspondence (Box 852, Folder 2)
      - The Youth Project - A-P (Box 852, Folder 3-5)
      - The Youth Project - R-Z (Box 853, Folder 1-2)
      - Campaign for Political Rights (Box 853, Folder 3)
      - Caribbean Basin Information Project (Box 853, Folder 4-5)
      - Contributions (Box 855, Folder 1)
      - Contributions - Alida R. Dayton (Box 855, Folder 2-3)
    - Camps, 3
      - Youth Camps - A-Z (Box 854, Folder 1)
      - Fresh Air Fund (Box 854, Folder 2)
    - Homes, 4
      - Youth Homes - A-Z (Box 854, Folder 3)
  - X-Z, 1982-1986; 37; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - X-Y - Miscellaneous (Box 843, Folder 2)
    - Z - Miscellaneous (Box 854, Folder 4)
  - Audiovisual materials, 38; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
    Sound recordings; Moving Images
    - The President's Commission on Executive Exchange - A Step to Tomorrow, Part II, U-matic (Box 1, Tape AV 13022)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - The Gardeners of Eden - A Case Study of Development in Botswana, 1986 March 26; Betamax; 33 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 13023)
      A Rick Lomba film
    - Caribeau Central American Action Dinner, Plimsoll Club, featuring David Rockefeller, 1985 March 18; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 13024)
    - DUB, International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - "Something In Common", 1983 November 4; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 13025)
    - David Rockefeller - Commission on Security and Economic Assistance - Foreign Assistance: An Issue for All Americans, c. 1985; U-matic (Box 1, Tape AV 13026)
      CSIS-Georgetown University, 1800 K. Street N.W., Washington, D.C.
    - David Rockefeller - Addresses/Remarks - Keynote Address: David Rockefeller, Chairman, Americas Society, 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15835)
    - David Rockefeller - Addresses/Remarks - 40 Visual Arts Network: Expanding Exhibition Collaboration Among Canada, the U.S. and Latin America, 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15836)
    - Consider the Alternatives, No. 548, The Freeze Debate, Sane Media Productions, Sane Education Fund, 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV15837)
    - KRLC - MX Missle Conference Report, Stan Holmes moderator, 1982 June 19; 1/4 inch audio cassette; 7 minutes, 15 seconds (Box 1, Tape AV 15838)
    - KRLC - Excerpts: Nuclear Arms Race Programs, 1/4 inch audio cassette; 10 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 15839)
    - S. Holmes (Stan Holmes), KRLC - Sample Reports and Interviews, 1982 October; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15840)